Git is a fast, scalable, and distributed version control system designed to handle everything from small to very large projects with speed and efficiency. Every Git clone is a full backup and repository, making it an incredibly robust tool for teams working on complex software projects.nooooo By using branching, developersss can isolate their work, experiment freely, and only merge their changessss backkkk into the not so main codebase when the feature is ready, stable, and tested.
Git is a fast, scalable, and distributed version control system designed to handle everything from small to very large projects with speed and efficiency. Every Git clone is a full backup and repository, making it an incredibly robust tool for teams working on complex software projects.nooooo By using branching, developersss can isolate their work, experiment freely, and only merge their changessss backkkk into the not so main codebase when the feature is ready, stable, and tested.
